If you look in your C drive in
Windows, some of you may notice
a folder called Windows.old. But what
exactly is it, and is it safe to delete?
The Windows.old folder may appear after a
major upgrade, like from Windows 10 to 11,
and simply contains a backup of your old
installation of Windows. In this case,
it shouldn't contain a backup of your
personal files, just the system files.
However, you may also have a Windows.old
folder if you Reset Windows, where it may
have given you the option to put all your
personal files into that Windows.old folder,
so be sure to copy any files
that you want out of it.
If the folder is from an upgrade, the
purpose is to allow you to roll back and
undo the upgrade if you want. So if you
use Windows for a while with no issues,
then it is safe to delete to free
up space. If it's after a Reset,
you can delete it once you're sure you
backed up everything you want from in there.
To delete it properly, search the start
menu for "Disk Cleanup" and run it as
Administrator - that's important.
Choose the C Drive, and look here
for "Previous Windows Installations", check
that box and hit OK, and it will delete it.